Guide to the National Education Association-Film, Audio, and Video records, 1938-2011 NEA1010.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Promotional Material, 1938-2011, bulk 1954-2011; 1954-2011; Series 3; 187 Linear Feet
  - Every Child is a Winner, 1974; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3559, Folder 2)
  - Excerpt from David Brinkley's Journal, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3972, Folder 16)
  - Excerpts from program #7 - "Can't We All Just Get Along: Dealing with Hate & Bias in School", March 26, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 6)
  - Experiment in Excellence, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 15)
  - Explorer1 1, May 7, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 7)
  - Explorer1 2, May 7, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 8)
  - Explorer1 3, May 7, 2001; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 8)
  - "Explosion of a Myth" Filmstrip and Script, 1957; Series 3 (Box 3671, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 File 1 Filmstrip
  - Fairfax Education Association - Original Master, August 27, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 7)
  - Federal City College [Educational Pamphlets], Undated; Series (Box 4832, Folder 14)
  - Fight for Better Schools, undated; series 3 (Box 4559, Folder 1)
  - Filmstrip, Every Teacher.. An Active Political Citizen, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3657, Folder 2)
  - Final Edits - Great Adventure Auditions, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3559, Folder 1)
  - First B (Generic), May 31, 1985; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 28)
  - First Steps, undated; Series 3; BETCAM video tape (Box 4058, Folder 22)
  - Focus 1996 (Intro - Keith), Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 8)
  - Focus '96, July 1, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 7)
  - Focus '96 - "The Faculty Lounge: A Fantasy:, July 1, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 8)
  - Focus '96 - "Opening Segment", July 1, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 9)
  - Focus '96 - "Teaser #1", July 1, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 9)
  - Focus on Education Change: Charter School, Undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3965, Folder 1)
  - Focus on the Future, 1960; Series 3; Filmstrip; magnetic tape. (Box 3677, Folder 6)
  - Focus on Quality Instruction, Undated; Series 3; film (Box 3656, Folder 1)
  - Freedom.com Compilation Reel - Boc Chase Segments), November 2, 1999; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 7)
  - Freedom to Learn 1, 1954; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3865, Folder 4)
  - Freedom to Learn 2, 1954; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3864, Folder 4)
  - Friend of Education, June 11, 1992; Series 3 (Box 3965, Folder 2)
  - Friend of Education 1998 - Zell Miller, July 21, 1998; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3982, Folder 10)
  - The Forward Thrust, 1967; Series 1; Filmstrip; 7 1/2 IPS. (Box 3677, Folder 3)
  - Funding for Tag End Credit, September 18, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3999, Folder 10)
  - "Future Search", December 6, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 1)
  - Future Search (Compton MTV Version), December 16, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 2)
  - Future Search (Marketing Version), January 10, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 3)
  - Future Stars Sculpture, July 3, 1987; Series 3; BETCAM video tape (Box 4058, Folder 23)
  - Garroway, Gitlin, Culligan - Messages to NEA Officers - Fall 1957, Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 39)
  - Garroway, Gitlin, Culligan - Messages to NEA Officers - Fall 1957, series 3 (Box 4504, Folder 1)
  - Garroway, Gitlin, Culligan - Messages to NEA Officers - Fall 1957 (Transferred), Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 40)
  - Garroway, Gitlin, Culligan - Messages to NEA Officers - Fall 1957 (Transferred), series 3 (Box 4505, Folder 1)
  - George Fischer, Former NEA President 69-71, Interview, June 5, 2008; Series 3; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 60)
  - The Golden Key, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3865, Folder 3)
  - Good Schools Make a Difference, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 8)
  - Good Schools Make a Difference, undated; series 3 (Box 4554, Folder 1)
  - Gov. Kerry, November 21, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 1)
  - Govt. Relations NEA-PAC '94, April 26, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 7)
  - Graham Green - "I Have a Dream", June 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 2)
  - Great Adventure and What is a School, 1955; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 41)
  - Great Adventure and What is a School, 1955; series 3 (Box 4506, Folder 1)
  - GR Gary Timmons Video Message to VEA-CCT, March 9, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 8)
  - GR Narration - "How Do They Measure Up?", June 11, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3979, Folder 8)
  - Grady Yancey, Georgia Association of Educators Interview; George Fisher, Past NEA President Interview, June 29-July 1, 2011; Series 3; Audio Cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 72)
  - Guide and Script "A Chance to Serve", Undated; Series 3 (Box 3671, Folder 4)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 FIle 4 Filmstrip
  - Hancock - MEA Ad Campaign #1, June 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 3)
  - Hancock - MEA Ad Campaign #2, June 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 4)
  - Hancock - MEA Ad Campaign #3, June 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 5)
  - Happy Birthday, SBE!!!, November 15, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii State Teachers Association "HSTA Open", August 29, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 9)
  - HCR "'94 HCR Awards Finner" with Maya Angelou, June 27, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 10)
  - HCR Awards - Anita Perez Ferguson "I Have a Dream", May 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 6)
  - HCR Awards Banquet 2002, August 14, 2002; Series 3; VHS (Box 4015, Folder 24)
  - HCR Banquet '97 - Sarah Brady, June 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 7)
  - HCR Ban. Shoot #6 - Candace Gringrich, June 4, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 8)
  - HCR Baquet Show - Sharon Draper (TOTY) (MCK Speech), May 14, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 9)
  - HCR Shoot - E. Emeal "I Have a Dream", May 23, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4000, Folder 10)
  - HCR Shoot - Ted Kennedy, June 5, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 1)
  - HCR "Time for Reflection", May 12, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 11)
  - HCR Video - "Congressman Jesse Jackson Jr.", May 16, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 2)
  - HCR Video - "I Have a Dream" (Master A), June 26, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 3)
  - HCR Video - "I Have a Dream" (Master B), June 26, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 4)
  - Helen Bain Interview, Former NEA President, July 9, 2008; Series 3; Pate-Bain, Helen; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 56)
  - Heritage Series Interviews with Al-Tony Gilmore, June 28-29, 2010; Series 3; Three audio cassette tapes and manuscript notes from interviews. (Box 3851, Folder 6)
    Includes interviews with the following: Agnes Chavis, North Carolina Bobbie Duncam, Texas Jean Deboshi, Hawaii Jane Sakamoto, California Christine E. Nowak, New York Edithe Fulton, New jersey Velma Jones, Tennessee Eunice Norton, Alabama Geraldine McNeil, North Carolina Sid johnson, Arkansas Iris Harris, Maryland
  - Hey, Look at me!, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3864, Folder 3)
  - Higher Education CD (Audio), November 8, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education CD (Barry Sterns), October 25, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education (Bob Chase Soundbits), January 15, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4017, Folder 10)
  - Higher Education CD Clips, September 4, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3980, Folder 1)
  - Higher Education CD (Rachel Henderson), October 25, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education NEA Select Roll, September 17, 1986; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 18)
  - Hillary Clinton Talks Health Care at the White House, May 16, 1994; Series 3 (Box 3990, Folder 3)
  - Hillary Clinton Talks Health Care at the White House, May 16, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4100, Folder 7)
  - Hillary Show - Radical Right V.O. Transfer from 1/4" audio tape, December 8, 1993; Series 3 (Box 3884, Folder 10)
  - "Honoring Our Legacy of Inclusion: the NEA-ATA Merger", April 21, 2006; Series 3; VHS (Box 4015, Folder 25)
  - Honoring Our Legacy of Inclusion/The NEA-ATA Merger, 2006; Series 3 (Box 5064, Folder 5)
  - How Do They Measure Up? 1, June 17, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 1)
  - How Do They Measure Up? 2, May 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 2)
  - How Do They Measure Up? FINAL 1, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 8)
  - How Do They Measure Up? FINAL 2, June 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 3)
  - How Do They Measure Up? LOOP, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3980, Folder 2)
  - How Does My Child Learn to Read & Other Questions, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3864, Folder 2)
  - How Good Are Our Schools?, 1959; series 3 (Box 4566, Folder 1)
  - Human and Civil Rights Awards, June 23, 1993; Series 3 (Box 3965, Folder 6)
  - Human and Civil Rights Awards Banquet, 1996; Series 3 (Box 3964, Folder 8)
  - Human and Civil Rights Award Dinner Tape 1, 1991; Series 3 (Box 3965, Folder 7)
  - Human and Civil Rights Award Dinner Tape 2, July 5, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3965, Folder 8)
  - Human & Civil Rights "Radical Right Deceptions", February 1, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 12)
  - Idaho - Bob Chase Video Message to Robin Nettinga, June 11, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM Video Tape (Box 4001, Folder 9)
  - Idaho Education Association "Visioning", November 8, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 4)
  - IEA - "Interesting Times", February 25, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 4)
  - If the Shoe Fits...-Sound Filmstrip Stock No. 058-02160, 1969; Series 3; 33 1/3 LP Time: 12 Mins. Audible signal for Manual Equipment (Box 3662, Folder 11)
    Separated Materials found in Box 3664 File 7 2 Filmstrips
  - If We're So Good...Why Aren't We Better, 1974; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3864, Folder 1)
  - Ignorant and Free 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3865, Folder 1)
  - Ignorant and Free (Transferred), 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3974, Folder 18)
  - I Have a Dream - Chastity Bono (Plus: Favorite Teacher), undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 1)
  - I Have a Dream - Melissa Etheridge, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Education Assn. - "Rise", February 27, 1998; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 5)
  - Imagine, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4001, Folder 10)
  - Impact, 1964; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3559, Folder 4)
  - The Inauguration of Sam M. Lambert as Executive Secretary of the NEA Reel 1&2, October 20, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058C, Folder 3)
  - The Inauguration of Sam M. Lambert as Executive Secretary of the NEA Reel 1&2, October 20, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 14)
  - The Inauguration of Sam M. Lambert as Executive Secretary of the NEA Reel 3&4, October 20, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4059, Folder 4)
  - Incident on Wilson Street, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 1)
  - Incident on Wilson Street, undated; series 3 (Box 4516, Folder 1)
  - Incredible 65,000 Image Pak, Undated; Series 3; CD (Box 4015, Folder 26)
  - Influential Americans Part I, undated; series 3 (Box 4575, Folder 1)
  - Influential Americans Part 2, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 10)
  - Influential Americans Part 2, undated; series 3 (Box 4587, Folder 1)
  - In Focus, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 12)
  - International Global Campaign for Education, 2004; Series 3 (Box 4636, Folder 4)
  - Introduction to Professional Negotiations, Undated; Series 3; Pre-Recorded Program Filmstrip 3-3/4 IPS E.T. (Box 3665, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in Box 3664 File 2 Filmstrip
  - Invest In Education PSA, undated; Series 3; 16mm color film with soundtrack. (Box 3798, Folder 1)
  - Invest in Kids (Hispanic), July 2, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 19)
  - Invest in Kids (No Logos), June 30, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 20)
  - Invest in Kids (Public Service), June 18, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 21)
  - Involvement in Edudcation 1 (30 Seconds), undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 17)
  - Involvement in Education 2 (30 Seconds), undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3973, Folder 18)
  - Iowa Education Assoc. - "Special Education Funding" (Radio), April 18, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 3)
  - Iowa Education Association "Bob Chase Tribute to Angie King", February 28, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 13)
  - ISEA "Why School Reform", February 12, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 22)
  - It's Elementary (Edited Version) 1, February 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 5)
  - It's Elementary (Edited Version) 2, February 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 6)
  - It's Magic, Anaheim, California, 2002; Series 3; VHS Cassette Tape (Box 5081, Folder 6)
  - I Wish I Could, Kathy, 1962; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 13)
  - James Harris Interview, undated; Series 3; Harris, James A.; Three audio cassette tapes. (Box 3682, Folder 63)
  - Jane Saap - Human and Civil Rights Awards, 1991; Series 2; BETACAM video tape (Box 3966, Folder 4)
  - Jane Saap - sub-master, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3966, Folder 5)
  - Jimmy, 1966; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 10)
  - Joe Reed, Alabama, Interview, May 23, 2008; Series 3 (Box 3682, Folder 67)
  - Johnny on the Spot, 1957; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 11)
  - John Stocks Interview for Book, March 7, 2011; Series 3 (Box 3682, Folder 68)
  - John Wilson - "Interdepartmental Team Leader Welcome", October 23, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 4)
  - Joy Elmer Morgan Honored by Future Teachers of America in New York City, 1954; Series 3; 1800 Ft., 1 Mil Acetate Audio Tape (Box 3853, Folder 6)
    Morgan, Joy Elmer
  - Justice Brennan Award, July 13, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 5)
  - Kansas-NEA/Wyoming Educ. Assoc. Countdown Slates/Tags, February 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 7)
  - Keith Geiger Appreciation, July 5, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 6)
  - Keith Geiger, Former NEA President, Interview, July 11, 2008; Series 3; Geiger, Keith; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 62)
  - Keith Geiger Introduces "Cornerstone for the Future", March 8, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 6)
  - Keith Geiger Message to Empora State Teleworkshop, October 12, 1995; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 7)
  - Ken Melley Interview, February 14, 2011; Series 3; Melley, Ken; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 64)
  - Ken Melley-Timberlane Film, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3987, Folder 3)
  - Kennedy for Senate, October 7, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 14)
  - Kevin Forney Tribute, September 29, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3966, Folder 7)
  - Lamar Alexander (NEA Board Meeting, Washington Hilton), May 4, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 8)
  - Lambert, Sam 0043 - Announcement of Appointment, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3616, Folder 7)
  - Larry Somerson (On-the-street Interviews) - New Unionism, August 6, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 9)
  - Lauri Wynn Interview, April 23, 2008; Series 3; Wynn, Lauri; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 71)
  - Learning for Life, 1961; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 14)
  - Let's Help President Clinton Change America - Produced by Fenn King Murphy Communications, June 30, 1993; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3966, Folder 9)
  - Let's Take a Trip, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 15)
  - Leyendo por Todo el Pais - Read Across America Hispanic Radio PSA 1, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 10)
  - Layendo por Todo el Pais - Read Across America Hispanic Radio PSA 2, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 11)
  - Layendo por Todo el Pais - Read Across America Hispanic Radio PSA 3, undated; Series 3; Audio cassette tape (Box 4014, Folder 12)
  - Learning to Read, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058, Folder 2)
  - Linda Tar-Whelan, May 13, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4002, Folder 10)
  - Lionel Cartwright "Drop Out", April 2, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 8)
  - Lionel Cartwright "Drop Out" (Montana Education Association), April 2, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 23)
  - Lionel Cartwright (Generic) "Drop Out", March 12, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 24)
  - Lobby/Inte., May 30, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 9)
  - Lobby/Museum Animation, June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4019, Folder 1)
  - Lobby/Museum Animation FINAL, June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4018, Folder 10)
  - Lois Edinger, Former NEA President, Interview on Libby Loontz by Al-Tony Gilmore, March 4, 2008; Series 3; Edinger, Lois V.; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 59)
    Koontz, Elizabeth D. (Elizabeth Duncan)
  - Looking At Values, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_8318a057fbce6a57445955cfca7347d4)
  - Luther Jackson Middle School Event with Hillary Clinton - Fairfax, VA #1, March 12, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3966, Folder 10)
  - Luther Jackson Middle School Event with Hillary Clinton - Fairfax, VA #2, March 12, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3967, Folder 1)
  - Luther Jackson Middle School Event with Hillary Clinton - Fairfax, VA #3, March 12, 1996; Series 3 (Box 3967, Folder 2)
  - MA/CGR "Future Search", December 6, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3984, Folder 1)
  - MA/CGR "Future Search" (Compton MTV Version), Deccember 16, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 10)
  - MA/CGR "Future Search" (Marketing Version), October 1, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 9)
  - Major League Soccer "Get a Kick Out of Reading", undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 1)
  - Make a Mighty Reach, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 16)
  - Make a Mighty Reach 1, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4059, Folder 5)
  - Make a Mighty Reach 2, undated; Series 3 (Box 4059, Folder 6)
  - Make it Happen w/ NEA Tag, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4019, Folder 2)
  - Make It Happen: Teach, 1998; Series 3 (Box 4636, Folder 5)
  - Making Schools Safe, September 18, 1992; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3967, Folder 3)
  - Marian Wright Edelman - "I Have a Dream", undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 1)
  - Mary Futrell Friend of Education Award, July 11, 1989; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3967, Folder 5)
  - Mary Futrell Interview, Washington DC, with Al-Tony Gilmore, January, 2008; Series 3; Futrell, Mary; Audio cassette tape. (Box 3682, Folder 61)
  - Man and His Environment, Undated; Series (Box 3849, Film 1-inch type data_value_missing_426a83b9cad75e049676c8cdfd0e462b)
  - Massasschusetts Teachers Association "It's Our Profession! A Call to Action", April 12, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 25)
  - Massachusetts Teachers Association - "One Voice Kennedy" 1, October 11, 1994; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts Teachers Association - "One Voice Kennedy" 2, October 11, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts Teachers Association "One Voice Kennedy" 3, October 11, 1994; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 26)
  - A Matter of Equity 1, June 21, 1985; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 2)
  - A Matter of Equity 2, June 21, 1985; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4013, Folder 3)
  - "McCalls Teacher of the Year, 1959" Black/White Length: 7:00, Series 3; 16 mm (Box 3652, Folder 1)
  - MEA Ads - Warren (Tape #4), June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 3)
  - MEA Ads - Warren (Tape #5), June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 4)
  - MEA Ads - Warren (Tape #6), June 10, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 5)
  - MEA Presents...Services for All, Undated; Series 3 (Box 3674, Folder 1)
    Separated materials found in Box 3673 File 7 Filmstrip
    Michigan Education Association
  - Measure of a Nation, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 17)
  - The Measurement of a Leader (Short Version), September 14, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 6)
  - The Meeting Place, 1973; series 3 (Box 4525, Folder 3)
  - Membership is the Key, undated; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 7)
  - Mesa Education Assoc. - "Teacher Evaluation" 1, April 1, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 7)
  - Mesa Education Assoc. - "Teacher Evaluation" 2, April 1, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3983, Folder 8)
  - Messages that Work in Support of Public Education 1, July 25, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3980, Folder 3)
  - Messages that Work in Support of Public Education 2, July 25, 2000; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4029, Folder 19)
  - Michigan Education Assoc. "Why MEA?", September 16, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 16)
  - Michigan Education Association - "A Matter of Dignity" Raw Footage, Stoney Creek School, June 4, 1997; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3980, Folder 4)
  - Michigan Education Association "Special Message to ESP", June 6, 1994; Series 3; 1in magnetic tape (Box 4016, Folder 17)
  - Mike Makes His Mark, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 4058A, Folder 3)
  - Mike Makes His Mark, undated; Series 3; BETCAM video tape (Box 4058, Folder 24)
  - Mind Over Media (4 packages), May 24, 2001; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 8)
  - Miss America PSA/Generic Carolyn S. Sapp, April 1, 1992; Series 3; 1in magentic tape (Box 4028, Folder 27)
  - More Different than Alike, 1967; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 18)
  - More Than Voting, October 2, 1991; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 3967, Folder 7)
  - A Movie About Light, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 1)
  - Mr. Keith Geiger - Wash. Post, June 11, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4019, Folder 3)
  - Mr. Novak, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3994, Folder 11)
  - MSTA "Read Across America 2000", May 3, 2000; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 9)
  - Mt. Pleasant - MEA Ad Campaign, May 21, 1996; Series 3; BETACAM video tape (Box 4003, Folder 10)
  - Music's Generation, 1972; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 1)
  - Mutual Aid & Protection - Kent County Education Association, April 23, 1993; Series 3 (Box 3267, Folder 8)
  - My Laboratory of Life - Filmstrip, 33 1/3 rpm recorded narration, Guide and Script, Undated; Series 3; My Laboratory of Life Written and Narrated by Lawana Trout 33 1/3 rpm Long playing 11 min. 30 sec. (Box 3672, Folder 12)
    Separated materials found in Box 3670 FIle 11 Filmstrip
  - Mystery in N-13, undated; Series 3; 16mm film (Box 3986, Folder 2)